	<Mod
		name="Nemesis-Ability-Plus"
		description="
Ver 3.03

Note: If this mod is introduced, it should be placed above Noita Nemesis (and Nemesis Teams).
注意:このMODを導入する場合、Noita Nemesis（とNemesis Teams）より上に配置してください。

If you can read Japanese, you may want to see the Japanese explanation at the following URL.
日本語が読める方は、以下の記事に日本語での解説が乗っています。

https://note.com/hanrei_7/n/n65cd7bf13106

------------------------

More interference ability for Noita Nemesis.
For more information about Noita Together and Noita Nemesis (by SkyeOfBreeze), please click on the following link.

https://github.com/Noita-Together/noita-together/releases

The order in which the mods are placed is important. Be sure to place them according to the image at the top or the following instructions.

(1)[Nemesis-Ability-Plus]
(2)[Noita nemesis teams]
(3)[Nemesis prototype]
(4)[Noita Together]

------------------------

Additional Systems

Specification to prevent disable Kick on death mode from causing problems.
Dropouts cannot acquire abilities in any state, are always short-circuited, no enemies are sent to them, and their friendliness level is high.

Disabled inventory opening on its own when approaching perks without editing the wand.
The other players will be notified that you have defeated Kolmisilma.

------------------------

Ability Lottery(Silver Frame Abilities)

Does not erase other abilities when acquired this.
There is a random chance that you will get back half of the NP you paid at the time of purchase.

------------------------

Risky Ability(Red Ability)

Once you die and respawn, this ability will appear the next holy mountain.
What is needed to purchase this ability is HP, not NP.
The value to be consumed is as per the following formula.

n = Number of times Risky Ability is obtained.
m = Maximum HP at the time of entering the holy mountain.
HP consumed by payment : 10 + ( 10 * ( n + 1 ) ) + ( m * 0.1 )

------------------------

Dangerous Abilities(Gold Frame Abilities)

It also affects the person who acquired it at the time of this acquisition.
These effects are powerful, but must be handled with care.

------------------------

NP Perk Rerol

You can redraw perks by paying NP.
However, only one perk is redrawn.

------------------------

Helpful Booster

When you have acquired 3 or less abilities so far and you die, they will appear near the resurrection point.
It has the following effects for a period of 60 seconds.
・One-time HP increased by 15 points.
・One-time Spell refresher.
・Effect of one Faster Movement perk.
・Effect of concentrated mana.

In addition, there are additional benefits for even more disadvantaged players.

------------------------

Example of additional abilities

Power Rangers
 Defeated monsters will be resurrected once only in a gigantic form. The gigantic enemy explodes when it dies.
 Giant enemies nullify melee and fire and are resistant to projectile, explosion, and slice.

Sluggish Wand
 Instead of weakening the opponent's magic overall, it increases its lifespan and number of bounces.

Jigoku Disc
 It throws a sawblade, which flies and bounces around at high speed, into the opponent.

Deer You
 Exploding and non-exploding deer rain down on the opponent.

Cockroach Trap
 The sticky house stops the opponent's movement.

Poison Bomb
 It sends a huge poison bomb that explodes after 5 seconds.
 It is possible to escape the range by just moving normally, but even if you try to erase it with 'Projectile Eater' or something else, it will weak explode.

You Are Cyclops
 Add Perk 'Personal Plasma Beam' to the opponent.

FizzledOne's Grudge
 The effect is enhanced depending on how many 'Fizzeled's the effected player has acquired so far.
 The number of 'Fizzeled's obtained plus one type of bad status will be given for the length of time corresponding to the number of 'Fizzeled's obtained.
 The count of 'Fizzeled' earned is reset once the 'Fizzled One's Grudge' effect is received.

Parts of Omega1,2,3
 This is an ability that consists of three ABC's.
 When one, two, or three types are collected, the effects of Black hole, Giga black hole, and Omega Black Hole are triggered.

Incendiary Cloud
 It sends a cloud of fire, oil, and weak detonating projectiles raining down on the opponent.

The Three Musucketeers
 Four types of monsters are sent to the opponent: Peitsivartija, Salamurhaajarobotti, Robottikytta, and Heinasirkka.

Powerplant Men
 Five types of monsters are sent to the opponent: Vakoilija, Pysayttaja, Tarkkailija, Teloittaja, and Kyrmyniska.

The Illuminati
 Make the gauges in the upper right corner of the opponent's screen invisible.

Fake Items
 Fake items appear in the opponent's dungeon that are detrimental if acquired.

Poo Bomber
 There will be a stench of hell from the opposing projectiles.

Invis Projectiles
 For a certain period of time, the projectiles present on the opponent's screen becomes transparent.

And more ...

------------------------

Enhanced existing abilities

Tanks
 Previously, it only summoned some KK-Tankki's, but now it summons one additional IT-Tankki or one additional Laser-tankki.

Acid
 In addition to the conventional effect of acid being spread around, we have added the effect of Acid Trail.

Steve
 Added a random perk and berserk to the Stevari that is summoned.

Spike Drinks
 Changes were made to the type of liquid mixed in.

------------------------

"
		tags="quality of life"
		dont_upload_folders="FOLDER_TO_IGNORE1|FOLDER_TO_IGNORE2"
		dont_upload_files="FILE_TO_IGNORE1|FILE_TO_IGNORE2"
	> 
	</Mod>